Daniel Aiyelu

Date of birth: 20/02/1997 | Nationality: Nigerian (Nigeria) | Phone number:

(+49) 1627327713 (Mobile) Email address: aiyeludaniel@gmail.com LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-aiyelu-49045b8a/

Skype: live:.cid.88cfbf67e4eb4075

Address: Trierer Street 123, 52078, Aachen, Germany (Home)

About me:

Deadline-driven personality focused on overseeing projects from concept through final delivery. Successfully creates brand messages, strategies and key graphic productions. Resourceful and hardworking with vendor sourcing expertise and empowering leadership skills illustrated over 5 years of industry success, working both as a freelancer and for well established organizations.

WORK EXPERIENCE

10/07/2021 - 24/02/2022 Kiev. Ukraine

IT SUPPORT PRIME DATE

- · Installing, configuring and maintaining computers in large organisations
- · Providing direct user assistance
- Working for a business with contracts to maintain and repair computer hardware
- Working for a supplier of a software application for a specific business sector, such as retail, travel or pharmaceutical
- · Ensuring clients websites and applications stay up and running and offering technical support.

02/05/2019 - 30/01/2021 Lagos, Nigeria

WEB DEVELOPER FIDEPAD EDA

- · Producing clean, efficient code based on specifications
- · Testing and deploying programs and systems
- Fixing and improving existing software
- · Verifying and deploying programs and systems
- Troubleshooting, debugging and upgrading existing software
- · Gathering and evaluating user feedback
- Creating technical documentation for reference and reporting

06/02/2017 - 28/12/2018 Lagos, Nigeria

GRAPHICS WEB DESIGNER ACE DESIGNS

- Worked with customers to understand needs and provide excellent service.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems.
- Developed and implemented performance improvement strategies and plans to promote continuous improvement.
- Learned new skills and applied to daily tasks to improve efficiency and productivity.

02/05/2022 - CURRENT Lagos, Nigeria

FREELANCE FRONTEND DEVELOPER (REMOTE) EDU START

- 1. Developing user-friendly web applications using React.js and related libraries such as Redux, React Router, and Axios.
- 2. Collaborating with UX/UI designers to implement visually appealing and responsive designs.
- 3. Implementing reusable components and ensuring code quality through unit testing and code reviews.

- 4. Optimizing web application performance and user experience.
- 5. Integrating web applications with back-end APIs using RESTful API or GraphQL.
- 6. Debugging and resolving issues reported by users or detected during testing.
- 7. Keeping up-to-date with the latest web development trends and technologies.
- 8. Participating in team meetings and providing input on project requirements and timelines.
- 9. Maintaining and updating code documentation.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/05/2022 - 01/06/2022 Germany

CERTIFICATE OF GRADUATION Start Steps Digital Job Compass

Address Germany | Website https://startsteps.org/de/

24/05/2022 - 23/07/2022

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION Zero To Mastery(UDEMY)

Website https://zerotomastery.io/

16/09/2009 - 21/05/2012

WEST AFRICAN SENIOR SCHOOL CERTIFICATE Olorunfunmi Senior Grammar School, Idimu

06/09/2021 Ukraine

BSC (HONS) MANAGEMENT University of Finance, Kiev, Ukraine

Distance Online Learning

Address Ukraine | Field of study Management

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): OSOSO

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
UKRAINIAN	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1
RUSSIAN	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1
YORUBA	C2	C2	C2	C2	B2
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Programming

HTML5/CSS, Javascript RESTful api React Hooks / React Bootstrap / React Router /React Hooks PHP Laravel Angular.js (Basic)

Web, Graphics and UI/UX Design

Wordpress, UI/UX Architect Design tools (Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, Figma, Affinity) Corel Graphic Suite

Communications

IT Technical Support | Excellent skills in presentation softwares (Microsoft PowerPoint and Keynote) | Cus tomer Interaction, Customer Support